<resources>
    <string name="app_name">myDiem</string>
    <string name="activity_welcome.intro1">
        myDiem is an app that allows you to analyse your apps usages metrics and share that on the Streamr data Marketplace anonymously.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_welcome.intro2">
        Your anonymous data will be aggregated with many other users, creating a revenue sharing Community Product.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_welcome.intro3">
        You will automatically receive a portion of any revenue generated by the sale of that aggregate
        data and you will be able to withdraw your earnings to your digital wallet that will be created in the next few steps.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_transparency.header">
        Below are examples that MyDiem will collect
    </string>
    <string name="activity_transparency.access">
        Get a list of all applications that are stored on this device. \n \n
        Read about how much time you spend on each application. \n \n
        The application activity names and its model data usage \n \n
        Mobile device information like language and network type.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_transparency.request">
        myDiem will only collect app usage metrics like time spent on an app, when it was opened or
        closed, but it will never collect any action or information within any app.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_transparency.request2">
        In Order to allow this app to collect apps usage metrics,you need to grant it some permissons first.We take your privacey very seriously.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_transparency.authorize">
        Authorize Folder Access
    </string>
    <string name="activity_transparency.continue">
        CONTINUE
    </string>
    <string name="activity_transparency.back">
        BACK
    </string>
    <string name="activity_permission_stats.header">
        Grant app the permission to read apps metrics
    </string>
    <string name="activity_permission.allow">
        ALLOW
    </string>
    <string name="activity_permission.info">
        To track app usage metrics,please allow us to access media on your device.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_permission.info.location">
        You can decide to share anonymously your location data.This will allow you to receive additional revenue from this data,in addition to your app usege metrics.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_permission.info.location.add">
        You will alse have option to enabel location sharing later from within myDiem app settings.
    </string>
    <string name="activity_permission_stats.authorize">
        Authorize Metrics Access
    </string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="today">TODAY</string>
    <string name="week">WEEK</string>
    <string name="month">MONTH</string>
    <string name="all">ALL</string>

    <!-- <string name="menu_1">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_2">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_3">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_4">Tools</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>-->
</resources>
